School Dance is a comedy, music, drama film directed by Nick Cannon.
High schooler Jason has found his dream girl—the gorgeous Anastacia.
There’s just one problem: she doesn’t know he exists.
If he can win a spot on the school’s hottest
dance crew, Jason might have a shot.
But before he does, he’ll have to overcome his battle-ax of a mother, survive Anastacia’s gangsta
brother, and pass the crew’s initiation—in this fresh, sexy, and outrageously funny comedy.
Prairie Puff Man, played by Patrick Warburton.
Flaco, played by Wilmer Valderrama.
El Matador, played by Efren Ramirez.
Principal Rogers, played by Mike Epps.
Jason Jackson, played by Bobb'e J. Thompson.
Oscar, played by George López.
School Dance is a 2014 American musical comedy-drama film co-written,
produced, and directed by Nick Cannon in his directorial debut.
The film stars Bobb'e J.
Thompson, Luenell, Mike Epps, George Lopez, Lil Duval, Katt
Williams, Kevin Hart and Wilmer Valderrama.
The film was released on July 2, 2014, in select theaters, VOD, and Digital HD.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.